members1st.org 2014-04-07

# FACTS

                                                                                                              Rev.  03/2014
                      WHAT DOES Members 1st Federal Credit Union
FACTS                 DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                     how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                     understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                     have with us. This information can include:
                          Social Security number and income
                          account balances       and payment history
                          credit history         and credit scores
How?                 All ﬁnancial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons ﬁnancial companies can share their
                     customers' personal information; the reasons Members 1st Federal Credit Union
                     chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                               Does Members 1st
Reasons we can share your personal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                        FCU share?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                       Yes                             No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you                                Yes                             Yes
For joint marketing with other ﬁnancial companies                        Yes                             Yes
For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your transactions and experiences                      Yes                             No
For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your creditworthiness                                  No                        We don't share
For our afﬁliates to market to you                                       Yes                             Yes
For nonafﬁliates to market to you                                        No                        We don't share
To limit                  Call 800-237-7288    —our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) or
our sharing               Visit us online: www.members1st.org
                      Please note:
                      If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                      sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                      described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?            Call 800-237-7288 or go to www.members1st.org

Page 2
Who we are
                                    Members 1st Federal Credit Union
Who is providing this notice?
What we do
How does Members 1st FCU           To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information?   and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                   These measures include computer safeguards and secured ﬁles
                                   and buildings.
How does Members 1st FCU           We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?
                                       Open an account               or deposit money
                                       Pay your bills                or apply for a loan
                                       Use your credit or debit card
                                    We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                    bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?     Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                       sharing for afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                        about your creditworthiness
                                       afﬁliates from using your information to market to you
                                       sharing for nonafﬁliates to market to you
                                   State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                   limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing
                                    Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
for an account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Deﬁnitions
Afﬁliates                          Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   ﬁnancial and nonﬁnancial companies.
                                       Members 1st Insurance Services
                                         Members 1st Settlement Services
Nonafﬁliates                       Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   ﬁnancial and nonﬁnancial companies.
                                       We do not have any nonaffiliates.
Joint marketing                    A formal agreement between nonafﬁliated ﬁnancial companies that
                                   together market ﬁnancial products or services to you.
                                       Progeny Marketing Innovations, Inc.
                                        CUNA Mutual Insurance Society
                                        Fetch Insurance Services, LLC
Other important information
